

Evi Nur Annisa Jl Kantil 3 perumnas No.267, Yogyakarta 55281 082138854442 evi.annisa@students.amikom.ac.id https://www.linkedin.com/in/evinannisa/ https://github.com/evinannisaa

Summary

Hallo my name is Evi. I'm a college's student of Amikom's informatics engineering. I live in Yogyakarta. I have joined with three organization and I used to be a lab assistant of web design. Currently, I am running diploma degree an working on my portofolios. Also, I am still and counting to make a new journey and to be a better Evi each day. Take your time, check my resume and see my skills. Thank you.

Education

AMIKOM YOGYAKARTA UNIVERSITY

Diploma, Informatics Engineering. GPA 3.83

Yogyakarta, Indonesia 2019 - Present

- Teaching/Practicum Assistant
- Bidikmisi scholarship recipient
- Introduction to Computer division of Mobile Development
- Awarding Amikom Computer Club
- Committee of Penggalian Potensi Mahasiswa
- 3rd place Design UI/UX at "Gelar Karya Mahasiswa D3 Fakultas Ilmu Komputer Universitas Amikom Yogyakarta"

Work Experience

PT. Media Kreasi Abadi (MKA) Internship (MBKM) Frontend Developer

Balikpapan, Indonesia Feb 2022 – Jul 2022

- Learn frontend basics developers such as HTML, CSS, Http protocol, JavaScript, Using Version Control (git), Build Tools, Layouting and more
- Able to build web-based applications with react typescript and about basic javascript, basic react and also basic typescript
- Slicing UI/UX designs to HTML, CSS

GCM FOUNDATION (Geschool)

Yogyakarta, Indonesia Jan 2022 – Feb 2022

Freelance Frontend Developer

- Creating webpage layouts, code writing, and making adjustments based on client feedback
- Implemented UI and UX designs to web
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments

GCM FOUNDATION (Geschool) Internship Frontend Developer

Yogyakarta, Indonesia Sept 2021 – Jan 2022

- Implemented websites and landing pages from concept through deployment
- Assessed UX and UI designs for technical feasibility
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments

AMIKOM YOGYAKARTA UNIVERSITY

Yogyakarta, Indonesia Feb 2021 – Aug 2021

- **Practicum Assistant of Web Design 1**
 - Practice and explain HTML, CSS and JavaScript modules to students
 - Reviewing lessons or lectures with students on a one-on-one basis or in small groups
 - Supervising students in class and tracking attendance, grading assignments and calculating activity score

Leadership & Activities

BEM KM AMIKOM YOGYAKARTA UNIVERSITY Ministry of Advocacy

Yogyakarta, Indonesia Feb 2021 – Present

- Capture the aspirations of all amikom students
- Oversee internal and external issues on campus
- Establish communication with the Chancellor regarding student welfare needs
- Pioneer of the vaccination program, scholarship and all aspirations for Amikom students

Himpunan Mahasiswa Diploma Teknik Informatika Treasurer

Yogyakarta, Indonesia Sep 2020 – Dec 2021

- Oversee the general financial management of an organizing committee
- Plan and keep track of budgets within the organization, collect, deposit and keep track of funds write cheques and provide financial reports regularly

Ikatan Mahasiswa Bidikmisi Amikom Division of Entrepreneurship

Yogyakarta, Indonesia Nov 2020 – Nov 2021

- Responsible for developing creativity members of entrepreneurship
- Responsible for finding sources of financial income to achieve independence and prosperity

Portfolio

• Repository "buildwithangga" Slicing to HTML, CSS with Bootstrap:

https://github.com/evinannisaa/joinbwa

• Portfolio web:

https://evinannisa.github.io/eviannisa/ (not updated)

• Platform Education Parenting:

https://edufams.com

• Login page geschool:

https://madrasahdiy.net/ . http://gunungkidul.geschool.net/ . http://diy.geschool.net/

• Assesment Kompetensi Minimum:

https://github.com/AKM-geschool/akm-geschool.github.io

• Dribble (Design UI/UX)

https://dribbble.com/Evi_annisa

Skills and Interests

Skills: HTML CSS, JavaScript (React Js), UI/UX Design (Figma)

Language: Indonesian **Tools:** VsCode and Figma

Interests: UI/UX design, Android studio, JavaScript